>> Kyle Simpson: 如果你有一个像第 9 行那样的疯狂的呼叫站点呢 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What if you had
a really crazy call site like line 9?
9 行，我有个新关键词，我有个讲习班点，所以
On line 9, I have a new keyword,
I have a workshop dot ask, so
我有上下文对象。
I have a context object.
我有点束缚，在应用的范围下。
And I have dot bind, which under
the covers of course using apply.
我的四个规则中有三个是在同一个电话站点上匹配的。
I have three of my four rules
matched on the same call site.
我不是说你应该这样写个电话网站
I am not by the way suggesting you should
ever write a call site like that, but
它确实有效
it does actually work.
那么地球上的原因是什么，它怎么知道要用什么东西呢 ?
So why on Earth does it work, and
how does it know which thing to use?
如果多个规则与一个呼叫站点匹配，那么优先顺序是什么 ?
If more than one rule matches a call site,
what's the order of precedence?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好吧，你可以说服自己
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Well, there's a way
that you could convince yourself or
向您自己证明操作的顺序或优先顺序是什么。
prove to yourself what the order of
operations, or the order of precedence is.
但我要去简化手续告诉你
But I'm just gonna go ahead and
simplify, and tell you,
这就是提出这些问题的顺序。
this is the order to ask those questions.
从这里向前看如果你需要问自己我的关键字是什么
So from here forward, if you ever need
to ask yourself what is my thisKeyword
在调用此函数时将指出，这就是您确定该函数的方式。
gonna point out when this function gets
invoked, this is how you determine that.
>> Kyle Simpson: 对 thisKeyword 的确定是第一个关键字，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The determination for
the thisKeyword is, number one,
是新函数调用的函数吗 ?
was the function called with new?
如果是，那么新创建的对象将为 thisKeyword。
If so, the newly created object
will be the thisKeyword.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 第二，该函数是通过调用或应用来调用的吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Number two, is
the function called with a call or apply?
顺便说点，点绑定是这个规则的一个子，因为它也有应用。
And by the way dot bind is a sub of
that rule because it also uses apply.
如果是这样，那么将使用指定的上下文对象。
If so, the context object that
is specified will be used.
>> 凯尔辛普森: 如果不匹配，那么第三个，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If that doesn't match,
then number three,
在上下文对象 ( 如研讨会点 ) 上调用的函数吗 ?
is the function called on a context
object like workshop dot ask?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果是，请使用该对象。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If so, use that object.
如果这三种都没有应用，那么我们就会回到默认值。
And if none of those three have applied,
then we fall back to the default which
除严格方式外，对全局对象的缺省值。
says default to the global
object except in strict mode.
就是这四条规则它会完美地完全
That's it, just those four rules in that
order, and it'll perfectly and completely
回答所有关于我的关键字点有什么意义的问题 ?
answer every question that you may have
about what does my thisKeyword point at?